My body is doing better than expected.
身体状况比想象中好
Good morning.
早安
Nephrites!?
涅芙丽缇丝
When did you get here?
你什么时候在这里的
I was here the whole time.
我一直都在这里哦
The whole time?
一直?
How is your body holding up?
你的身体还好吗
The ring has the power
戒指的力量
to heal any injury.
也能治疗受伤的身体
You've been training so hard
为了赢过葛兰纳托殿下
so you can defeat Princess Granart.
你一直很努力吧
You can put it that way. I'm only doing my best.
算是吧 我想尽力而为
But honestly, I'll probably end up losing.
但老实说 我应该赢不了
With the ring's power,
只要用戒指的力量
you can win.
一定能赢的
Of course,
当然
it's best to have the princess' recognition.
能得到那位公主的认同最好
But the Ring King's mission
但戒王的使命
is to collect all the rings.
就只有得到戒指而已
For that, you must use any means necessary.
为此你必须不择手段
Well... I'm aware of that...
话是…这么说没错
A Ring Princess's duty is to assist the Ring King.
戒指公主的职责就是协助戒王
Lord Satou, simply follow your heart and do what you think is necessary.
佐藤陛下只要按照自己的想法 去做就行了
You are right.
你说得对
Thank you, Nephrites.
谢谢你 涅芙丽缇丝
I should try a little harder.
我会试着再自己努力一下
When I finally mustered my courage...
难得我稍微鼓起了勇气…
TALES OF WEDDING RINGS
《婚戒物语》
Whoa...
哦
You've improved a lot.
你进步很多呢
Does it mean I can win?
这样有办法赢吗
At least once out of ten tries?
十次赢个一次左右
That's not possible.
那是不可能的
I knew it.
我想也是
Your opponent isn't going to use these obvious attacks
对手不会像我刚刚那样
like I did just now.
老老实实对你挥剑
When you can counter that
等你能应付这种对手
and still pull off your moves earlier,
并做出刚才那样的动作
you might actually stand a chance.
才有取胜的机会
Well, at least you can win once
不过你现在至少
out of ten thousand tries.
有万分之一的可能性了
With the power from your rings,
接下来只要用戒指的魔法
she shouldn't be a problem.
应该就能搞定
Again!
那再来一遍
Is that the Ring King?
那就是戒王吗
They said Princess Granart has high expectations for him.
听说葛兰纳托大人满看好他的
She even let him touch her body.
听说还允许他摸了身体
What do you mean by that?
那是什么意思
She let him touch her body
允许他摸身体
so he could give her a scrub.
原来是要他搓澡的意思啊
But...
但是
that doesn't change the fact that Satou touched her.
佐藤最后还是摸了她吧
The body of that princess...
摸了那位公主的身体…
No!
不行…
Maybe it's time I stop saying no to that.
但我也许不能再继续说不行了
The Ring King is having a rematch with her?
戒王要再次挑战吗
We don't get this kind of fight every day.
真是难得的精彩好戏
Ouch...
好痛
She's insanely powerful.
也太强了吧
Ring King!
戒王
Princess!
公主
-Ring King! Go for it! -Princess Granart!
-戒王 上啊 -公主
Satou! Give it your best!
佐藤 尽力而为就好哦
What's the matter, Krystal?
怎么了 克莉丝朵
Aren't you going to cheer for him?
你不帮他加油吗
Satou has been training really hard lately
佐藤这几天
to earn Princess Granart's
为了得到那位公主的认同
recognition.
一直很努力哦
Does that even matter?
不被认同也无所谓
His job is to collect rings from princesses
他只要从我以外的公主手上
other than myself.
取得戒指不就好了吗
Just when I thought
本来想说运气好的话
I might have the chance to become a king...
也许有机会当上国王
Ring King, show us what you've got!
戒王 让我们看看你的厉害吧
That's not fair.
真卑鄙呢
He gets stronger with his ring.
只要得到戒指就能变强
A ring?
戒指?
Seize me if you desire more power.
如果想得到力量 就拿起我吧
Desire my power.
渴求我吧
Not going to change your mind, I presume.
你不打算改变心意吗
Yes.
嗯
I'll make you acknowledge my strength!
我要让你认同我
Hey, what are you doing?
喂 你想干嘛
Leave now.
快回去
Come another time if you want a rematch.
想重新挑战的话改天再来
Silence!
少啰嗦
Ring King.
戒王
You robbed me of my chance back in Lomka.
在洛姆加被你捷足先登了
I won't allow it to happen again!
但这次你休想得逞
Ring King, dodge!
戒王 躲开
Abyssal Creatures!
是深渊的魔物
That guy summoned the Abyssal Creatures!
那家伙竟然召唤出了魔物
Fire monsters?
是火之魔物吗
Stand back, Your Highness!
快退开 公主们
The catfolks have been training night and day
我们猫人族在深渊王的威胁远离后
for the resurrection of the Abyss King
也一直为他将来复活的那一刻
after he was defeated.
日以继夜努力训练
His forces are nothing to be scared of!
深渊王的军队根本没什么好怕的
Separate this zone from the others.
把这个区域和其他区域分离
We must keep the monsters here.
别让任何一只魔物逃出这里
Yes.
是
Run!
快走
Leave this area and find shelter!
离开这个区域去避难
Decouple the link now!
快分离
Yes!
是
It's time for the catfolks
我们猫人族
to show their might!
展现力量的时刻到了
A knight of the Abyss King.
深渊王的骑士吗
I've heard rumours about it.
我有听过传闻
It should be a worthy opponent.
够格当我的对手
I've been so bored after fighting the weak
一直跟很弱的对手较量
for so long.
我正觉得无聊呢
Granart!
葛兰纳托
Watch and learn!
你就在那里看着吧
I need to figure out a way to deal with his flame.
得想办法搞定他身上的火焰
All right. This should work.
很好 行得通
Wind magic!
就用风魔法
Ouch...
好痛
I thought the wind was strong enough to put out the flame.
我还以为只要用风吹散火焰就行了
I can take it from here.
这里就交给我吧
Don't be silly.
你在说什么
Your sword can't even cut that thing.
你的剑也碰不到他吧
Indeed.
没错
But I'm not going to give up just yet.
但我并不打算放弃
My people
我们一族
are descendants of the warriors who fought alongside the Ring King.
是与古代戒王并肩作战的战士后代
Since you are the Ring King of this generation,
既然你是这一代的戒王
fighting by your side
与你并肩作战
and protecting you until the very end
保护你到最后一刻
is our duty.
就是我们的使命
It doesn't matter how unreliable you are.
无论你是多么不可靠的男人
Gramps says
根据爷爷的说法
I still can't command the ring's magic at will.
我还无法好好驾驭戒指的魔法
But...
但是
If I can distract that thing
只要我专心引开他的注意力
and disperse its flame...
并吹散他身上的火焰…
It's too risky.
很危险哦
I'm a total wimp compared to you, Granart.
跟你比起来 我的确很弱
But there is something I can do!
即使如此 我也有能做到的事
I get it.
我明白了
Very well.
好吧
The rings are here!
戒指在这里
Come and get them!
放马过来吧
The rings...
戒指…
Not yet.
还没
Closer.
再来
Just a bit closer.
再靠近一点
Now!
就是现在
Granart!
葛兰纳托
I got this!
交给我吧
Ring King, finish it!
戒王 干掉他
Was the knight being controlled by the black ring?
又是被黑色的戒指操控了吗
Princess Granart!
葛兰纳托大人
We took out all the monsters.
我们把出现的魔物通通解决了
Well done.
辛苦了
Is everyone all right?
大家都没事吧
Yeah.
没事
The catfolks sure are strong.
猫人族真强呢
Huh? What happened to me?
奇怪 我是怎么了
Ring King.
戒王
It seems I underestimated you.
我好像有点太小看你了
You may lack the strength,
虽然现在还欠缺力量
but you possess the qualities of a king.
但你有成为戒王的资质
I acknowledge your worth.
我愿意认同你
You may become my husband.
当我的丈夫
It's inevitable.
这是无可奈何的事
This is the very reason why Satou is working so hard.
佐藤就是为此而努力的
No. Not yet.
不 还不行
I don't want you to recognise me.
我不是要你认同我
I want to earn it.
而是争取你的认同
Granart.
葛兰纳托
I'm challenging you to another fight.
我再次向你提出相亲
Let me confirm once again.
我再确认一次
The fight is over when one of us
有一方认输或无法战斗
is unable to battle.
就算分出胜负
Brace yourself!
我要上了
From the right...
右边吗
It came from the left!
是左边
Satou, calm down!
佐藤 冷静点
It's not over yet.
还没完呢
Why are you even doing this?
为什么要做这种事
She's already agreed to give you the ring.
人家都说要给他戒指了
You're such a fool.
简直像个笨蛋
Princess Krystal, won't you cheer for him?
克莉丝朵殿下不帮他加油吗
Lord Satou is fighting for your sake.
佐藤陛下一定是为了你才战斗的
For me?
为了我
Use the rings.
快用戒指的魔法
Are you going easy on me?
难道你是在小看我吗
No.
不是的
The rings are power I'm borrowing from Hime and Nephrites.
戒指的力量是跟小姬她们借来的
It's not my own power.
不是我自己的力量
Even if it helped me win,
就算靠那股力量赢了
I'm still the pathetic man who's lost in front of the girl he likes.
我依然是在喜欢的女生面前 狼狈输掉的男人吧
I'm trying to be the cool guy
我是为了最心爱的妻子
for the wife I love!
才想当一个帅气的男人
He really is
他真的…
a big oaf.
是个傻瓜呢
Satou!
佐藤
If you defeat Granart,
如果你打赢葛兰纳托
I'll have sex with you as your reward!
我就跟你上床当作奖励
Yeah!
好
How amusing.
真有趣
You are an amusing man.
你真是个有趣的男人
I'll assist you in this fight.
我就助你一臂之力吧
This voice is coming from the ring.
这个声音是戒指传出来的
I'll see through her next move.
我来代替你看穿她的下一步吧
Focus on my voice.
你专心听我的声音
Doing so
这么一来
will let you act faster than her in a split second.
你就能瞬间比她早一步行动
But that's...
可是这样的话…
Don't worry.
放心吧
This isn't the power of the Ring Princesses.
这不是戒指公主的力量
Consider this an opportunity you've earned yourself.
把这当成是你自己带来的好机会
I don't quite get it, but I know what to do.
虽然搞不太懂 但我知道了
Very well.
这样就对了
What's wrong?
怎么了
Are you shocked by her cheer?
该不会是那声加油让你吓到了吧
Brace yourself!
我要进攻了
She disappeared!
消失了
Above you.
在上面
What?
什么
Satou!
佐藤
He did it!
他做到了
Lord Satou is amazing!
佐藤陛下太厉害了
He actually won.
他赢了
What was that just now?
刚刚那是怎么回事
What...
什…
Great work, Ring King.
做得好 戒王
You're the first to have defeated me.
你是第一个赢过我的人
I must give you the recognition you deserve.
看来我只能真心认同你了
All right. Let's make a baby.
好了 我们马上来生孩子吧
In Needakitta,
在尼妲齐达
the winner has the utmost respect.
获胜者拥有最崇高的地位
The defeated must serve the winner wholeheartedly.
输掉的人身心都要臣服于他
Hold on...
等等 那个…
I'll ask my servant to get things ready.
我现在就叫手下们做准备
Wait.
等一下
Why should we wait?
有什么好等的
I'm already your wife.
我已经是你的妻子了
Are you saying my body isn't good enough for you?
还是说 你不满意我的身体吗
No.
不是的
I already have a promise with someone else.
因为我已经跟别人先约好了
Hime and I made a promise.
我和小姬先约好了
Satou did great.
佐藤真的很努力
This is his reward.
这是给他的奖励
We are husband and wife anyway. It's something we do.
我们是夫妻 本来就该做这种事
Hime. Can we...
小姬 那个
Satou?
佐藤
get down to business?
快做吧
I'm going to let him have his way with me.
我接下来就要让他对我乱来了
All right, Satou.
好吧 佐藤
Let's do it.
来吧
Satou?
佐藤?
Hime's boobs...
小姬的胸部…
I see.
对哦
He used the rings' power
他用了戒指的力量
and fought so hard.
之后又那么努力战斗
You looked cool today, Satou.
你今天很帅哦 佐藤
Good morning.
早安
My darling.
老公
When did I fall asleep?
我什么时候睡着的
You were so feisty last night, Satou.
佐藤 你昨天好猛哦
What...
什…
I don't remember a thing.
我什么都不记得了
Nothing happened last night.
昨晚什么都没发生哦
Nephrites!?
涅芙丽缇丝?
I was awake and watching the whole time.
我一直醒着在这里观察
After all, it's my turn next.
因为下一个就轮到我了
Your turn?
下一个?
After her, it's my turn!
然后再下一个就是我了
Granart was here too?
连葛兰纳托都在
Princess Granart, it's time.
葛兰纳托大人 时间到了哦
All right.
好
You should be there too.
你们也一起来吧
We are holding a wedding.
接下来要举行婚礼
The people of Needakitta
我们尼妲齐达一族
have returned to the Ring King
又再次回到戒王底下
and become his fellow warriors once again!
成为与他并肩作战的战士了
She finally found the right man.
看来她找到一个好对象了啊
I was worried she'd never find a good suitor.
之前我还担心她会嫁不出去呢
Ring King.
戒王
You said you wanted to earn my recognition.
你说过要让我认同你吧
I'm glad you said it.
那句话让我很开心
So...
那个
I know.
我知道
You read my movement perfectly.
你完全掌握了我的动向
It wasn't a coincidence.
不管那是单纯的巧合
That was something else.
还是别的东西造成的
Your victory
那场比赛的胜利
is the result of your determination.
都是你不放弃所带来的结果
That's all that I need.
这样我就满足了
Hime!
小姬
Why did you gulp down the whole cup?
你干嘛突然猛灌酒啊
How should I know?
我哪知道
Satou.
佐藤
Stop making me worry.
你快点让我放心啦
I was really happy at that moment.
我那时候真的很高兴
You cheered for me.
因为你帮我加油了
But I want to finish that thing with you
不过我想等回到原来的世界
after I'm back in my world.
再跟你好好做那件事
This world is too unusual for me.
对我来说 这里终究不是平凡的世界
If we are to develop this relationship,
如果要发展关系
I want us to carry on
我想在原来的世界
in my world.
好好跟你一起走下去
Satou...
佐藤…
I don't think it's right
而且我认为不应该把这种事
to use this as a substitute or a means to love.
当作是某种代替品或恋爱手段
Thanks.
谢谢
It's a relief to hear that.
我觉得轻松多了
However...
不过
I still want to reward you for your hard work.
我还是想给为我努力的你一些奖励
Is there anything you want to do
你有没有想要我做的事
or want me to do?
或想做的事
I can grant you one wish.
我可以实现你的一个要求
I want...
那我想要…
I want to touch your boobs.
揉你的胸部
I want to touch your boobs to my heart's content!
我想要尽情揉你的胸部
I... I guess it can't be helped.
真…真拿你没办法
Satou, you're a perv.
佐藤你好色
Can I?
可以吗
Fine. Go ahead.
请摸吧
Granart!
葛兰纳托
Nephrites!
涅芙丽缇丝
I can't stand it! You're taking too long!
讨厌 真会拖拖拉拉
I'm already 18 years old.
我已经18岁了
Most of my people get married before that age.
在猫人族里算晚婚了
-Stop making me wait. -Princess Krystal, look at that.
-别让我再继续等下去了 -克莉丝朵殿下 你看那个
Cat powder!?
木天蓼?
I don't mind how we do it as long as we do it.
我不在意任何形式
That is how the Ring King still remains a virgin.
就这样 戒王守住了自己的贞操